sorry
I'm looking for a puppy
I can leave a poster in case you find
please
if you find
lost today no
actually he's not lost it's not
he can be walking with the best dog walker in town
in case it's me
thank you very much
thank you brother
valeu bye bye
I'm here
I already have enough
and that's it my Instagram brings it together
am I then
now i'm waiting to see if i get any messages
if anyone is interested
dog walk during the week
and to be able to call me so I can start undertaking
face
I washed clothes
it's bro I'm trying to use gym space
to be able to promote my work
is on
it's hard doidão
and that's it
but at least it was enough to wash it right bro
so it's smooth
speaking softly
because I'm not training
and
still have to eat
and have 1 money left to invest
in order to undertake
girl weighs right here
please
thank you saw
thank you
The Maya
everywhere is GO they be like